

PROFILE

I am a programmer with more than four years of experience cum in creating and developing desktop and web applications for groups and companies.

Furthermore, I am a web, logo, and banner designer. Moreover, trying to improve my skills and experience in my design and my professional field, which is programming, every day by learning new topics on the latest websites and worldwide educational resources, including YouTube, Stack Overflow, and medium.

On the other hand, I can translate texts, articles and so on.

CONTACT

PHONE: (+98)933 535 6068

WEBSITE:

Arya Gorjipour/ ArySmart - Index (epizy.com)
EMAIL:

Arygorji.arygorji.pour@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Playing video games writing Storytelling Taking courses in various fields

ARYA GORJIPOUR

Computer programmer & web developer

EDUCATION

Islamic Azad University Karaj Branch

2021 - current

Undergraduate computer engineering student.

Iran Language Institute Advance degree in English

013 - 2022

Proficiency in English (translation of texts, speaking)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Poya Host Full-stack developer & assistant programmer

2018 - 2021

Work as freelance and tech consultant.

IPO Full-stack developer

2020 - 2021

Work as freelancer and web developer.

SKILLS

